Quick question. Can we agree to stop using the word attack to describe someone disagreeing with
someone? And while we're at it, can we throw in there, tear down? I don't know. I feel like I see
quite a bit where if someone posts something and you disagree with them and you voice that,
that people will qualify that as you're attacking them or you are tearing them down when you're
literally just responding to the thing that they posted in a contrary manner, but without adding
the extra little colors. Cause you know, people do like to add the extra little colors. Or if you're
like, oh yeah, I don't know why that person's doing that. I've seen people qualify that as tearing down.
But to me, I feel like those are really strong words. Attack and tear down to me needs to include
things like dehumanizing somebody, belittling, calling people out their name. Have y'all witnessed
this? Do you feel the same way as I do? Or do you feel like at the end of the day, if somebody puts
up a post or makes a statement and you disagree with that statement, then it falls under attacking,
tearing down. Let me know your thoughts in the comments. Cause honestly, I'm feeling attacked by
attack.